Mss.B.F327
American Philosophical Society
- George Washington to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1781 April 30; No. 1609
- George Washington to Artemus Ward, 1776 March 1; No. 1610
- George Washington to Bushrod Washington, 1793 February 8; No. 1611
- George Washington to George Augustine Washington, 1783 September 11; No. 1612
- George Washington to Samuel Washington, 1776 October 18; No. 1613; Remarks: "We are...upon the Eve of something very important; what may be the Issue, Heaven alone can tell. I will do the best I can, and leave the rest to the supreme director of Events."
  David Library Item Number: 1613; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- George Washington to Anthony Wayne, 1780 November 14; No. 1614
- George Washington to Henry Wentworth, 1775 October 5; No. 1615
- George Washington to Anthony Walton White, 1778 December 6; No. 1616
- George Washington to Edward Wigglesworth, 1779 March 11; No. 1617
- George Washington to Samuel Williams, 1798 January 10; No. 1618
- George Washington to John David "Wilper" Woelper, 1773 November 30; No. 1619
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1778 August 17; No. 1620
- George Washington to David C. Claypoole, 1780 June 30; No. 1621
- George Washington to the Bank of Columbia, 1799 November 18; No. 1622
- George Washington, 1776 January 9; No. 1623
- Potomac Company, 1787 February 28-April 15; No. 1624
- George Washington to Robert Lewis, 1799 June 17; No. 1625
- Joseph Ravara to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1793 May 10; No. 1626
- George Washington for Lord Thomas Fairfax, 1750 November 26; No. 1627
- George Washington for Thomas Lindsey, 1751 March 19; No. 1628
- George Washington for George Neavil, 1750 October 30; No. 1629
- George Washington for Thomas Wiggans, 1750 April 24; No. 1630
- Will of George Washington, 1876; No. 1631; 1.0 vol.
- Society of Friends to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1789 October 3; No. 1632
- United States, President (George Washington) to Joshua Wentworth, 1791 March 4; No. 1633
- George Washington and others to Alexander Hamilton, 1795 February 14; No. 1634
- George Washington to Hassan Bashaw, 1796 June 13; No. 1635
- George Washington and Martha Washington to Robert Morris, 1790 March 27; No. 1636
- United States, President (George Washington) to William Miller, Jr., 1796 November 18; No. 1637
- George Augustine Washington to James "Abeal" Abeel, 1780 February 12; No. 1638
- Hannah Bushrod Washington to a miller, 1795 October; No. 1639
- John Augustine Washington to Hannah Bushrod Washington, 1786 September 12; No. 1640
- Lawrence Washington to David Stuart, 1803 July 7; No. 1641
- Martha Dandridge Custis Washington to Anna Maria Dandridge Bassett, 1761 April 18; No. 1642
- William Augustine Washington to Hannah Bushrod Washington, 1790 November 9; No. 1643
- Massachusetts, Provincial Congress, 1775 June 27; No. 1644
- Andrew Steel, 1774 December 31-1779 August 6; No. 1645
- John Thomas to Anthony Wayne, 1778-1780 December 8; No. 1646
- Anthony Wayne to David Logan, 1781 January 16; No. 1647
- Anthony Wayne, 1784; No. 1648
- Anthony Wayne to James Budden, 1784 March 25; No. 1649
- Anthony Wayne to Patrick Carr, 1782 June 26; No. 1650
- Anthony Wayne to Persifor Frazer, 1776 November 24; No. 1651
- Anthony Wayne to Francis Johnston, 1780 May 18; No. 1652
- Anthony Wayne to John Lacey, 1778 March 4; No. 1653
- Anthony Wayne to Joseph Reed, n.d.; No. 1654
- Anthony Wayne, 1777-1784; No. 1655
- Anthony Wayne to the clothier general, 1795 October 4; No. 1656
- Anthony Wayne to All civil and military officers, 1776 December 4; No. 1657
- Plunket Fleeson to Anthony Wayne, 1775 September 8; No. 1658
- Plunket Fleeson, 1775 August 26; No. 1659
- John Buchanan and others to Anthony Wayne, 1777 July 26, 27; No. 1660
- Gabriel Wayne, mariner to William Sandwith, mariner, 1737 August 13; No. 1661
- Samuel Blachley Webb to Barnabus Deane, 1782 May 26, 27; No. 1662
- George Weedon to ________, 1791 December 9; No. 1663
- Benjamin Weld, 1790 July 1; No. 1664
- John Wereat, 1780 June 1; No. 1665
- William West to Josias Clapham, 1789 April 25; No. 1666
- Samuel Wharton and William Trent to Robert Callender, 1771 July 23; No. 1667
- John Wheately, 1785 April 10; No. 1668
- Comfort Wheaton to Asa Waterman, 1777 July 20; No. 1669
- John Wheelock, on behalf of the trustees of Dartmouth College to George Walton, 1786 April 1; No. 1670
- Truman Wheler, 1780 March 6; No. 1671
- William White to George Washington, 1775; No. 1672
- William White to Mr. ______ Cuts, 1776 October 3; No. 1673
- Stephen Whiting, on behalf of Stephen Smith, 1778 May 31; No. 1674
- Samuel Williams to Samuel Holton, 1793 February 18; No. 1675
- Samuel Williams to Samuel Holton, 1793 March 3; No. 1676
- William Williams to Peter Cott, 1790 March 2; No. 1677
- ______ Williams to Mr. _____ Kingsberry, 1793 August 5; No. 1678
- William Williams to Anthony Wayne, 1778 August 18; No. 1679
- Andrew Williamson to Samuel Elbert?, 1779 April 1; No. 1680
- Francis Willis, Jr. to Charles Carter, 1745 February 3; No. 1681
- William Wilmot to Robert Burnett, 1782 July 26; No. 1682
- Abel Wilder to his wife, 1775 May 6; No. 1683
- Goodwin Wilson to Henry Jackson, 1778 October 22; No. 1684
- John Wilson to Jasper Yeates, 1776 February 24; No. 1685
- Anna Winslow to Elizabeth Dering, No. 1686
  Microfilm target that decribes the following sixteen letters.
- Anna Winslow to Elizabeth Dering, 1778 January 29; No. 1687
- Anna Winslow to Elizabeth Dering, 1778 June 23; No. 1688
- Anna Winslow to Elizabeth Dering, 1779 December 8; No. 1689
- Anna Winslow to Elizabeth Dering, 1781 January 30; No. 1690
- Anna Winslow to Elizabeth Dering, 1782 August 2; No. 1691
- Anna Winslow to Elizabeth Dering, 1783 March 10; No. 1692
- Anna Winslow to Mary Dering, 1778 February 15, 23; No. 1693
- Anna Winslow to Mary Dering, 1783 March 9; No. 1694
- Anna Winslow to Mary Dering, 1783 May 22; No. 1695
- Anna Winslow to Mary Dering, 1784 January 26; No. 1696
- Anna Winslow to Mary Dering, 1784 May 11; No. 1697
- Anna Winslow to Mary Dering, 1787 September 11; No. 1698
- Anna Winslow to Mary Dering, 1788 April 30, May 1; No. 1699
- Anna Winslow to Mary Dering, 1784; No. 1700
- Anna Winslow to Mr. _____ Dering, 1762 November 24; No. 1701
- Anna Winslow to the Dering family, 1780 July 18; No. 1702
- Noah Wiswell to John Clark, 1760 March 17; No. 1703
- Rev. John Witherspoon to William Hyslop, 1793 February 7; No. 1704
- Oliver Wolcott to Peter Cott, 1789 November 12; No. 1705
- Oliver Wolcott, Jr. to Henry Hollingsworth, 1790 March 6; No. 1706
- Oliver Wolcott, Jr. to James McHenry, 1800 July 18; No. 1707
- David Wolfe to Alexander Hamilton, 1791 June 16; No. 1708
- Benjamin Ruggles Woodbridge to Benjamin Lincoln, 1777 September 20; No. 1709
- Moses Woodward to the Commissary of Prisoners at St. Johns, 1781 August 25; No. 1710
- David Wooster, 1775 June 13-20; No. 1711; 1.0 vol.
- James Wadsworth, by order of Gen. Joseph Spencer, 1776 November 27; No. 1712
- Asa Worthington to Ebenezer Foote, 1779 February 4; No. 1713
- Asa Worthington to Ebenezer Foote, 1779 February 11; No. 1714
- Asa Worthington to Ebenezer Foote, 1779 May 28; No. 1715
- Asa Worthington to Ebenezer Foote, 1779 August 8; No. 1716
- Asa Worthington to Ebenezer Foote, 1779 August 11; No. 1717
- Asa Worthington to Ebenezer Foote or Asa Bigelow, 1779 December 8; No. 1718
- Benjamin Wynkoop to Levi Hollingsworth, 1793 April 16; No. 1719
- Abraham Yates, Jr. to Alexander Hamilton, 1793 September 26; No. 1720
- New York, City of Albany, Mayor (Abraham Yates, Jr.) to the New York Legislature, 1794 March 19; No. 1721
- Abraham Yates, Jr. to ________, 1793 September 18; No. 1722
- Abraham Yates, Jr., on behalf of the Common Council of Albany, N.Y. to Philip Schuyler, 1793 September 23; No. 1723
- Abraham Yates, Jr. to Philip Schuyler, 1793 September 26; No. 1724
- Christopher P. Yates to Charles and George Webster, 1799 May 28; No. 1725
- Leonard Dorsey, 1783 June 17; No. 1726
- Guy Young to Edward Dunscomb, 1783 September 12; No. 1727
- Guy Young to Edward Dunscomb, 1783 October 8; No. 1728
- Paul Zantzinger to Jasper Yeates, 1788 May 5; No. 1729
- Alexander Hamilton to Samuel Hodgdon, 1794 September 23; No. 1730
- Thomas Jefferson to the Governor of Georgia Edward Telfair, 1793 September 9; No. 1731
- Thomas Jefferson to James Greenleaf, 1793 March 25; No. 1732
- Charles Lee to Sidney Lee, 1781 December 11; No. 1733
- Gouverneur Morris to William Constable, 1797 July 7; No. 1734
- Abraham Ten Broeck to George Clinton, 1779 October 14; No. 1735
- George Washington to Mathew Carey, 1789 May 21; No. 1736
- _________ to George Washington?, 1776 August 4; No. 1737
- James Madison, Jr., Theodorick Bland, Jr. and Arthur Lee to Benjamin Harrison, 1782 September 3; No. 1738
- David Stuart to George Washington, 1799 January 4; No. 1739
- John Hancock to all Continental officers and others whom it may concern, 1777 October 19; No. 1740
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben to Thomas Jefferson, 1781 January 30; No. 1741
- George Washington to Anthony Wayne, 1780 December 28; No. 1742
- Thomas Abbot to the State of Massachusetts, 1780 July 9; No. 1801
- New Jersey, 1776 November-1777 March; No. 1802
  Related Archival Materials note
  Same manuscript as No. 1
- Abigail Adams to Thomas B. Adams, 1795 April 26; No. 1803
- Abigail Adams to Thomas B. Adams, 1814 May 10; No. 1804
- John Adams to Edme Jacques Genet, 1778 December 30; No. 1805
- John Adams to Richard Henry Lee, 1785 February 8; No. 1806
- John Adams to Thomas Loring, Jr., 1823 January 3; No. 1807
- John Adams to Dr. Benjamin Rush, 1806 January 25; No. 1808
- John Adams to Cotton Tufts, 1797 June 14; No. 1809
- John Adams to Mercy Otis Warren, 1787 December 25; No. 1810
- John Adams to William Wirt, 1818 January 5; No. 1811
- John Adams to William Wirt, 1818 January 23; No. 1812
- John Quincy Adams to Rufus King, 1797 October 18; No. 1813
- Samuel Adams to Pierre-Auguste Adet, 1795 July 28; No. 1814
- Charles Alexander to John Mitchell, 1776 March 13; No. 1815
- James Anderson to Clement Biddle, 1800 April 24; No. 1816
- Marriot Arbuthnot to George Phillips?, 1777 October 14; No. 1817
- Benedict Arnold, 1779 April 1; No. 1818
- Henry Babcock, 1776 February 14-1785 January 28; No. 1819; 1.0 vol.
- Elijah Backus to Asa Backus, 1779 April 21; No. 1820
- William Bacon, 1776 August 21; No. 1821
- Battle of Bunker Hill, n.d.; No. 1822
- George Benson to Welcome Arnold, 1779 May 4; No. 1823
- William M. Betts to John Fisher, 1779 April 5; No. 1824
- Owen Biddle to John Davis, 1779 May 28; No. 1825
- Jack Rathbone (Dr. Joshua Ebenezer Rathbone Birch) to Peter DeWitt, 1799 February 27; No. 1826
- Samuel Blodget, Jr. to John Dewhurst, 1792 February 25; No. 1827
- William Bradford to Joseph Reed, 1779 May 25; No. 1828
- Philip B. Bradley, 1778 March 5; No. 1829
- Thomas Brattle to Thomas Mumford, 1782 September 9; No. 1830
- George G. Brewer, 1830 November 16, 26; No. 1831
- John Brownlow to George W. Lewis, 1784 September 8; No. 1832
- Charles Burdett to William Fitzmaurice Petty, Lord Shelburne, 1782 July 5; No. 1833
- James Burnside to Moore Furman, 1778 October 28; No. 1834
- Aaron Burr to William W. Woolsey, 1800 February 24; No. 1835
- Aaron Burr to ________, 1807 December 7; No. 1836
- John Canfield to John DeWitt, Jr., 1779 January 29; No. 1837
- Charles Carroll of Carrollton, 1765 December 8-1766 March 17; No. 1838; 1.0 vol.
- James H. Causten to Thomas Jefferson, 1825 October 11; No. 1839; As agent for the claimants who suffered losses by the depredations French cruisers and tribunals from 1793 to 1800, points out in detail the circumstances surrounding the claim and requests Jefferson's advice; includes a letter from S[amuel] Smith, [n.d.], regarding the claim, and a copy of Jefferson's letter to Smith, [22 Oct. 1825]: expresses regret that because of old age and involvement in the establishment of the University [of Virginia], he cannot attend to the matter.
  David Library Item Number: 1839; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- J_______ Chew to Mrs. Betty Washington Lewis, 1792; No. 1840
- Richard Clark to Val Peirs, 1750 May 29; No. 1841
- George Clinton to Nicholas Fish, 1784 March 19; No. 1842
- George Clinton to Frederick Haldimand, 1784 March 19; No. 1843
- Joseph H. Colquitt to Henry Augustine Washington, 1844 July 9; No. 1844
- Connecticut, Windham County, Town of Pomfret, 1765 December 25; No. 1845
- John Connell to Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette, 1824 March 1; No. 1846
- Moses Contine to Timothy Pickering, 1783 February 14; No. 1847
- Henry Seymour Conway to the Governor (Samuel Ward) and Company of Rhode Island, 1766 March 31; No. 1848
- Francis Corbin to George Washington, 1798 July 14; No. 1849
- Pierre-Francois Cornic Dumoulin to Louis XVI, king of France or Antoine-Raymond-Jean-Gualbert-Gabriel de Sartine, comte d'Alby, 1777 November 11; No. 1850
- Nathanael Cotton to George Grenville, 1768 October 20; No. 1851
- Job Cushing to Thomas Fearing, 1787 May 16; No. 1852
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1850 October 17; No. 1853
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1851 August 12; No. 1854
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1851 August 20; No. 1855
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1851 September 15; No. 1856
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1851 December 13; No. 1857
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1852 January 20; No. 1858
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1852 February 28; No. 1859
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1852 March 20; No. 1860
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1852 April 25; No. 1861
- George Washington Parke Custis to Benson J. Lossing, 1852 May 19; No. 1862
- Silas Deane to Charles-Henri-Theodat, comte d'Estaing, 1779 August 14; No. 1863
- Silas Deane to Jonathan Williams, Jr., 1777 November 28, 29, December 2; No. 1864
- William Duer to John DeWitt, Jr., 1781 June 25; No. 1865
- Daniel Dulany to Robert Carter, 1769 January 28; No. 1866
- William Dunwoodies, on behalf of William Duer to John DeWitt, Jr., 1782 January 21; No. 1867
- Jean-Baptiste Vigoureux? Duplessis to George Washington, 1786 July 20; No. 1868
- Francis Willis, Jr., 1773 February 20-1774 November 30; No. 1869
- Nicholas Fish to Richard Varick, 1779 May 21; No. 1870
- Nicholas Fish, 1782 December 14-1783 February 15; No. 1871; 1.0 vol.
- William Fish, 1776 January 16; No. 1872
- William Hunter to Messrs. Fitzgerald and Peers, 1780 August 28; No. 1873
- Ebenezer Flagg to Benjamin Bourne, 1781 February 25; No. 1874
- Peter Fontaine to John Fontaine, 1765 July 8; No. 1875
- Tench Francis to Henry Drinker, 1794 May 23; No. 1876
- Benjamin Franklin to Charles William Frederick Dumas, 1780 June 5; No. 1877
- Benjamin Franklin to John Ellicott, 1763 April 13; No. 1878
- Benjamin Franklin to John Ellicott, 1764 June 23; No. 1879
- Benjamin Franklin to William Strahan, 1762 July 20; No. 1880
- William Franklin to Samuel Smith, 1768 May 5; No. 1881
- William Galvan to William Bingham, Matthew Clarkson, and Henry Brockholst, 1782 July 24; No. 1882
- Edmond-Charles-Edouard Genet to Jacques-Jerome-Anacharsis Brissot de Warville, 1820 June 22; No. 1883
- Number of citizens of Georgia, Savannah and its vicinity to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1791 May 13; No. 1884
- John Graham to John Fitzgerald, 1780 September 21; No. 1885
- John Gray to Lawrence Washington, 1842 November 17; No. 1886
- Nathanael Greene to Charles Harrison, 1782 January 25; No. 1887
- Nathanael Greene to John Wallace, 1779 July 5; No. 1888
- Nathanael Greene to George Washington, 1780 January 21; No. 1889
- Nathanael Greene to George Washington, 1780 September 23; No. 1890
- Shays' Rebellion, 1786-1787; No. 1891
  See also Nos. 1982, 2030, 2064, and 2092.
- Rev. Enoch Hale, 1775-1782; No. 1892; 10.0 vols.
- Alexander Hamilton to Nathaniel Appleton, 1790 December 13; No. 1893
- Alexander Hamilton to the Governor of Massachusetts (Samuel Adams), 1794 August 18; No. 1894
- Alexander Hamilton to Elizabeth Schuyler Hamilton, 1803 March 11; No. 1895
- Alexander Hamilton to the collectors of the customs, 1793 August 4; No. 1896
- John Hancock to "Dolly" (Dorothy Quincy Hancock), 1778 June 20; No. 1897
- Isaac Harris to Thomas Harwood, Jr., 1775 October 20; No. 1898
- William Heath to Henry Jackson, 1780 January 11; No. 1899
- Virginia, Henrico County Court to Henry Augustine Washington, 1843; No. 1900
- Virginia, Henrico County Sheriff to Henry A. Washington, 1844; No. 1901
- Patrick Henry, 1777 April 9; No. 1902
- Patrick Henry, 1784 December 30; No. 1903
- Patrick Henry to Thomas Madison, 1780 August 23; No. 1904
- Patrick Henry to William? Plum, 1778 May 26; No. 1905
- Patrick Henry to ________, 1777 November 12; No. 1906
- Battles of Trenton and Princeton, No. 1907
- Ruth Hopkins to George Hopkins, 1765 November 10; No. 1908
- Robert William Hughes to Henry Augustine Washington, 1847 December 13; No. 1909
- Henry Hulton to ________, 1770 May 4; No. 1910
- Regarding David Humphreys, 1796; No. 1911
- David Humphreys to Hassan Bashaw, 1796 August 3; No. 1912
- David Humphreys to Mathew Carey, May 6; No. 1913
- David Humphreys to Ebenezer Gray, 1780 September 10; No. 1914
- Samuel Huntington to Joseph Reed, 1780 May 24; No. 1915
- William Channing, William Ellery, Jr. and others to Ruth Champlin, 1797 February 22; No. 1916
- John Jay to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1779 August 16; No. 1917
- Thomas Jefferson to Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1795 December 26; No. 1918
- Thomas Jefferson to Pierre-Jean-Georges Cabanis, 1803 July 13; No. 1919
- Thomas Jefferson to Daniel Call, 1799 August 15; No. 1920
- Thomas Jefferson to Henry Dearborn, 1804 March 3; No. 1921
- Thomas Jefferson to John H. Freeman, 1807 January 5; No. 1922
- Thomas Jefferson to Jeremiah A. Goodman, 1812 March 1; No. 1923; Gives instructions for procuring and planting seeds and for sending a yoke of steers for hauling.
  David Library Item Number: 1923; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to John Laval, 1822 June 5; No. 1924; Requests information about an order for specified books by classical authors.
  David Library Item Number: 1924; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to Messrs. LeRoy, Bayard, and Company, 1823 July 18; No. 1925; Discusses the discharge of Jefferson's bond and the payment of interest on it.
  David Library Item Number: 1925; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to Albert and John W. Picket, 1818 April 10; No. 1926; Declines a subscription to their publication, The Academician.
  David Library Item Number: 1926; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to Henry Remsen, Jr., 1793 September 11; No. 1927
- Thomas Jefferson to David Rittenhouse, 1784 November 11; No. 1928
- Thomas Jefferson to David Rittenhouse, 1790 June 12; No. 1929
- Thomas Jefferson to David Rittenhouse, 1793 September 6; No. 1930
- Thomas Jefferson to William Short, 1804 November 10; No. 1931
- Thomas Jefferson to Robert Smith, 1801-1809; No. 1932
- Thomas Jefferson to Littleton W. Tazewell, 1801 January 28; No. 1933
- Thomas Jefferson to Charles Thomas, 1780 May 10; No. 1934
- Thomas Jefferson to the Secretary of the Navy Paul Hamilton, 1812 December 21; No. 1935; Asks him to have faith in the testimony of Jefferson's friend, who recommends a man for a position, and apologizes "for the frequency of these applications which is often impossible for me to decline."
  David Library Item Number: 1935; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to James Warren, 1786 February 8; No. 1936
- Thomas Jefferson to the Commissioners of Washington, D.C., 1802 January 7; No. 1937
- Thomas Jefferson to Richard Rush, 1821 August 14; No. 1938; Thanks him for sending books and for finding a reliable bookseller in London who will procure books when the library of the University [of Virginia] is commenced, and includes a list of books Jefferson wants for himself; mentions the "chaste architecture" of the new university, which will be open in a year or two, and discusses a candidate for the professorship of modern languages; mentions that there is little to communicate from "our peaceable plain sailing country"; informs him that "the distresses produced by the sudden diminution of our paper medium continue, and have produced great revolutions in the fortunes of individuals, greater...than was produced by the Revolutionary war"; informs him that "the Missouri question...is lulled by the acceptance and execution by that state of the condition required by Congress" [the Missouri Compromise]; comments that the Spanish American colonies "will be as independant as they chuse" and speculates on the type of government they will adopt; includes notations in Rush's handwriting.
  David Library Item Number: 1938; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to James D. Barry, 1807 June 25; No. 1939
- Thomas Jefferson to John Barnes, 1801 October 6; No. 1940
- Daniel of St. Thomas Jenifer to William Paca, 1782 December 5; No. 1941
- Thomas Johnson, Jr. to Samuel Purviance, Jr., 1775 June 13; No. 1942
- Joseph Jones to George Washington, 1789 November; No. 1943
- Henry Knox to George Washington, 1782 September 2; No. 1944
- Tadewz Andre Bonawentura Kosciuszko to John Barnes, 1801 May 30; No. 1945
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to Pierre-Etienne (Peter Stephen) Du Ponceau, 1831 September 28; No. 1946
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to Richard Henry Lee, 1778 July 6; No. 1947
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to Morgan Lewis, 1828 December 29; No. 1948
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to James McHenry, 1805 June 4; No. 1949
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to Nicholas Fish, 1828 May 6; No. 1950
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette to Philippe-Henri, marquis de Segur, 1783 December 20; No. 1951
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Philip Hone, 1831 October 31; No. 1952
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette, 1778 March 14; No. 1953
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette, 1831 May 10; No. 1954
- David Sears to Welcome Arnold, 1781 October 11; No. 1955
- William Ledyard to Jabez Huntington, 1778 September 7; No. 1956
- William Ledyard to Jabez Huntington?, 1779 February 4; No. 1957
- C.F. Lee, Jr. to Alexander Brown, 1879 April 19; No. 1958
- C.F. Lee, Jr. to Alexander Brown, 1881 February 9, May 31; No. 1959
- C.F. Lee, Jr. to Alexander Brown, 1881 May 24; No. 1960
- C.F. Lee, Jr. to Alexander Brown, 1881 June 1; No. 1961
- C.F. Lee, Jr. to Alexander Brown, 1891 July 31; No. 1962
- Charles Lee to his sister Sidney Lee, 1771 August 9; No. 1963
- Charles Lee to Jonathan Trumbull, Nicholas Cooke, James Bowdoin, and the President of the Council of New Hampshire (Meshech Weare), 1776?; No. 1964
- Henry Lee to William Augustine Washington, November 27; No. 1965
- Henry Lee to William Augustine Washington, 1796? February 21; No. 1966